{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "-1, -3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -3\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 4x + 4 \u003d 1\nFactor\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 1\nExtract the square root\nx + 2 \u003d √(1) or x + 2 \u003d -√(1)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 4x + 3 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(6) - 3, -√(6) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 12x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 6\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 6\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(6) or x + 3 \u003d -√(6)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 12x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -5", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 14x \u003d -20\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -10\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 9/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 9/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(9/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(9/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 14x + 20 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 12x \u003d -9\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 4x + 4 \u003d 1\nFactor\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 1\nExtract the square root\nx + 2 \u003d √(1) or x + 2 \u003d -√(1)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 12x + 9 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(6) - 3, -√(6) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -3\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 6\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 6\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(6) or x + 3 \u003d -√(6)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 6x + 3 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -4", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n4x^2 + 20x \u003d -16\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -4\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 9/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 9/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(9/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(9/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n4x^2 + 20x + 16 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(13)/2 - 7/2, -√(13)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -9\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -9\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 13/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 13/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(13/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(13/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 7x + 9 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(3) - 2, -√(3) - 2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -1\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 4x + 4 \u003d 3\nFactor\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 3\nExtract the square root\nx + 2 \u003d √(3) or x + 2 \u003d -√(3)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 4x + 1 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(3) - 3, -√(3) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 12x \u003d -12\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 3\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 3\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(3) or x + 3 \u003d -√(3)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 12x + 12 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(17)/2 - 5/2, -√(17)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 17/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 17/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(17/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(17/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 5x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 5x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(145)/10 - 5/2, -√(145)/10 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 25x \u003d -24\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -24/5\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 29/20\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 29/20\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(29/20) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(29/20)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 25x + 24 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(3)/3 - 2, -√(3)/3 - 2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 12x \u003d -11\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -11/3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 4x + 4 \u003d 1/3\nFactor\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 1/3\nExtract the square root\nx + 2 \u003d √(1/3) or x + 2 \u003d -√(1/3)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 12x + 11 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -4", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 15x \u003d -12\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -4\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 9/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 9/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(9/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(9/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 15x + 12 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 5x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 10x \u003d -12\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 10x + 12 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(7)/2 - 5/2, -√(7)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 10x \u003d -9\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -9/2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 7/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 7/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(7/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(7/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 10x + 9 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(6) - 3, -√(6) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 30x \u003d -15\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 6\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 6\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(6) or x + 3 \u003d -√(6)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 30x + 15 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(7)/2 - 5/2, -√(7)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 10x \u003d -9\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -9/2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 7/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 7/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(7/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(7/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 10x + 9 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(3)/2 - 3/2, -√(3)/2 - 3/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 6x \u003d -3\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -3/2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 3x + 9/4 \u003d 3/4\nFactor\n(x + 3/2)^2 \u003d 3/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 3/2 \u003d √(3/4) or x + 3/2 \u003d -√(3/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 6x + 3 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(17)/2 - 7/2, -√(17)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 14x \u003d -16\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -8\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 17/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 17/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(17/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(17/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 14x + 16 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(2) - 3, -2√(2) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -1\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 8\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 8\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(8) or x + 3 \u003d -√(8)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 6x + 1 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(21)/2 - 5/2, -√(21)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -1\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 21/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 21/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(21/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(21/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 5x + 1 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -6", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 14x \u003d -12\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 25/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 25/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(25/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(25/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 14x + 12 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(13)/2 - 5/2, -√(13)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -3\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 13/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 13/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(13/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(13/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 5x + 3 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 15x \u003d -18\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 15x + 18 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5)/2 - 5/2, -√(5)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 15x \u003d -15\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -5\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 5/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 5/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(5/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(5/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 15x + 15 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -5", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n4x^2 + 28x \u003d -40\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -10\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 9/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 9/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(9/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(9/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n4x^2 + 28x + 40 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n4x^2 + 20x \u003d -24\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n4x^2 + 20x + 24 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3, -4", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 21x \u003d -36\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -12\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 21x + 36 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(11)/2 - 5/2, -√(11)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n4x^2 + 20x \u003d -14\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -7/2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 11/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 11/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(11/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(11/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n4x^2 + 20x + 14 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(13)/2 - 5/2, -√(13)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 25x \u003d -15\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 13/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 13/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(13/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(13/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 25x + 15 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(2) - 3, -2√(2) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 12x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 8\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 8\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(8) or x + 3 \u003d -√(8)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 12x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 6x \u003d -4\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 3x + 9/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 3/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 3/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 3/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 6x + 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(13)/2 - 7/2, -√(13)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 14x \u003d -18\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -9\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 13/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 13/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(13/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(13/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 14x + 18 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(2) - 2, -√(2) - 2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 4x + 4 \u003d 2\nFactor\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 2\nExtract the square root\nx + 2 \u003d √(2) or x + 2 \u003d -√(2)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 4x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(3) - 3, -√(3) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 3\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 3\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(3) or x + 3 \u003d -√(3)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 6x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 5x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(7) - 3, -√(7) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 12x \u003d -4\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 7\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 7\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(7) or x + 3 \u003d -√(7)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 12x + 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(6) - 3, -√(6) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 18x \u003d -9\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 6\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 6\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(6) or x + 3 \u003d -√(6)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 18x + 9 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(3) - 3, -√(3) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 12x \u003d -12\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 3\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 3\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(3) or x + 3 \u003d -√(3)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 12x + 12 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(3) - 3, -√(3) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 3\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 3\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(3) or x + 3 \u003d -√(3)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 6x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(7) - 3, -√(7) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 7\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 7\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(7) or x + 3 \u003d -√(7)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 6x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(7) - 3, -√(7) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 18x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 7\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 7\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(7) or x + 3 \u003d -√(7)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 18x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5)/2 - 5/2, -√(5)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -5\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -5\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 5/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 5/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(5/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(5/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 5x + 5 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(2) - 2, -√(2) - 2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 8x \u003d -4\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 4x + 4 \u003d 2\nFactor\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 2\nExtract the square root\nx + 2 \u003d √(2) or x + 2 \u003d -√(2)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 8x + 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -6", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 25/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 25/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(25/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(25/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 7x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(2) - 3, -2√(2) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n4x^2 + 24x \u003d -4\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 8\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 8\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(8) or x + 3 \u003d -√(8)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n4x^2 + 24x + 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(21)/2 - 5/2, -√(21)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 10x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 21/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 21/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(21/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(21/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 10x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5)/2 - 3/2, -√(5)/2 - 3/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 6x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 3x + 9/4 \u003d 5/4\nFactor\n(x + 3/2)^2 \u003d 5/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 3/2 \u003d √(5/4) or x + 3/2 \u003d -√(5/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 6x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -5", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -10\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -10\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 9/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 9/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(9/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(9/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 7x + 10 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(13)/2 - 5/2, -√(13)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n4x^2 + 20x \u003d -12\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 13/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 13/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(13/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(13/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n4x^2 + 20x + 12 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(37)/2 - 7/2, -√(37)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 35x \u003d -15\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 37/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 37/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(37/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(37/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 35x + 15 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(185)/10 - 5/2, -√(185)/10 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 25x \u003d -22\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -22/5\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 37/20\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 37/20\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(37/20) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(37/20)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 25x + 22 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n4x^2 + 20x \u003d -24\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -6\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n4x^2 + 20x + 24 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(33)/2 - 7/2, -√(33)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -4\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -4\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 33/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 33/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(33/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(33/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 7x + 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(6) - 3, -√(6) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -3\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 6\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 6\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(6) or x + 3 \u003d -√(6)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 6x + 3 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(21)/2 - 5/2, -√(21)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 15x \u003d -3\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 21/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 21/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(21/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(21/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 15x + 3 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(2) - 2, -√(2) - 2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 4x + 4 \u003d 2\nFactor\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 2\nExtract the square root\nx + 2 \u003d √(2) or x + 2 \u003d -√(2)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 4x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(41)/2 - 7/2, -√(41)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 41/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 41/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(41/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(41/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 7x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 3x + 9/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 3/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 3/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 3/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 3x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(13)/2 - 5/2, -√(13)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 10x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 13/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 13/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(13/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(13/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 10x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -5", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 12x \u003d -10\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -5\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 4\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 4\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(4) or x + 3 \u003d -√(4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 12x + 10 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 6x \u003d -4\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 3x + 9/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 3/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 3/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 3/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 6x + 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 15x \u003d -10\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 3x + 9/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 3/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 3/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 3/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 15x + 10 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(2) - 3, -√(2) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -7\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -7\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 2\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 2\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(2) or x + 3 \u003d -√(2)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 6x + 7 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -4", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -8\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -8\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 1\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 1\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(1) or x + 3 \u003d -√(1)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 6x + 8 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(505)/10 - 5/2, -√(505)/10 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 25x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -6/5\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 101/20\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 101/20\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(101/20) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(101/20)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 25x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(6) - 3, -√(6) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 18x \u003d -9\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 6\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 6\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(6) or x + 3 \u003d -√(6)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 18x + 9 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(2)/2 - 5/2, -√(2)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n4x^2 + 20x \u003d -23\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -23/4\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 1/2\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 1/2\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(1/2) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(1/2)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n4x^2 + 20x + 23 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -5", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 14x \u003d -20\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -10\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 9/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 9/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(9/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(9/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 14x + 20 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(21)/2 - 5/2, -√(21)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n4x^2 + 20x \u003d -4\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 21/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 21/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(21/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(21/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n4x^2 + 20x + 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 3x + 9/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 3/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 3/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 3/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 3x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5)/2 - 7/2, -√(5)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -11\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -11\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 5/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 5/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(5/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(5/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 7x + 11 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 12x \u003d -9\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 4x + 4 \u003d 1\nFactor\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 1\nExtract the square root\nx + 2 \u003d √(1) or x + 2 \u003d -√(1)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 12x + 9 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(41)/2 - 7/2, -√(41)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 14x \u003d -4\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 41/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 41/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(41/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(41/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 14x + 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(33)/2 - 7/2, -√(33)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 35x \u003d -20\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -4\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 33/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 33/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(33/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(33/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 35x + 20 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5)/2 - 7/2, -√(5)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 14x \u003d -22\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -11\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 5/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 5/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(5/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(5/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 14x + 22 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(165)/10 - 5/2, -√(165)/10 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 25x \u003d -23\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -23/5\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 33/20\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 33/20\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(33/20) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(33/20)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 25x + 23 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -4", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n4x^2 + 24x \u003d -32\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -8\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 1\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 1\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(1) or x + 3 \u003d -√(1)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n4x^2 + 24x + 32 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(5)/2 - 7/2, -3√(5)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 35x \u003d -5\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 45/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 45/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(45/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(45/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 35x + 5 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5)/2 - 5/2, -√(5)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 15x \u003d -15\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -5\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 5/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 5/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(5/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(5/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 15x + 15 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5)/2 - 3/2, -√(5)/2 - 3/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 6x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 3x + 9/4 \u003d 5/4\nFactor\n(x + 3/2)^2 \u003d 5/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 3/2 \u003d √(5/4) or x + 3/2 \u003d -√(5/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 6x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5)/2 - 7/2, -√(5)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 21x \u003d -33\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -11\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 5/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 5/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(5/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(5/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 21x + 33 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(7) - 3, -√(7) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 7\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 7\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(7) or x + 3 \u003d -√(7)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 6x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(6) - 3, -√(6) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 30x \u003d -15\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 6\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 6\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(6) or x + 3 \u003d -√(6)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 30x + 15 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(7)/2 - 5/2, -√(7)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 10x \u003d -9\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -9/2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 7/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 7/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(7/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(7/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 10x + 9 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(13)/2 - 5/2, -√(13)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 10x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 13/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 13/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(13/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(13/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 10x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(5)/2 - 7/2, -3√(5)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 21x \u003d -3\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 45/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 45/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(45/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(45/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 21x + 3 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(41)/2 - 7/2, -√(41)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 14x \u003d -4\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 41/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 41/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(41/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(41/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 14x + 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(2) - 3, -2√(2) - 3", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -1\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -1\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 8\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 8\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(8) or x + 3 \u003d -√(8)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 6x + 1 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5)/2 - 5/2, -√(5)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 15x \u003d -15\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -5\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 5/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 5/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(5/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(5/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 15x + 15 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(19)/2 - 5/2, -√(19)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n4x^2 + 20x \u003d -6\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -3/2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 19/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 19/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(19/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(19/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n4x^2 + 20x + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(13)/2 - 7/2, -√(13)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n2x^2 + 14x \u003d -18\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -9\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 13/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 13/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(13/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(13/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n2x^2 + 14x + 18 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -5", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 18x \u003d -15\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 6x \u003d -5\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 6x + 9 \u003d 4\nFactor\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 4\nExtract the square root\nx + 3 \u003d √(4) or x + 3 \u003d -√(4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 18x + 15 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(2) - 2, -√(2) - 2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 4x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 4x + 4 \u003d 2\nFactor\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 2\nExtract the square root\nx + 2 \u003d √(2) or x + 2 \u003d -√(2)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 4x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1, -2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -2\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 3x \u003d -2\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 3x + 9/4 \u003d 1/4\nFactor\n(x + 3/2)^2 \u003d 1/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 3/2 \u003d √(1/4) or x + 3/2 \u003d -√(1/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 3x + 2 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(13)/2 - 5/2, -√(13)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -3\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -3\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 13/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 13/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(13/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(13/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\nx^2 + 5x + 3 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5)/2 - 5/2, -√(5)/2 - 5/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n5x^2 + 25x \u003d -25\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 5x \u003d -5\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 5x + 25/4 \u003d 5/4\nFactor\n(x + 5/2)^2 \u003d 5/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 5/2 \u003d √(5/4) or x + 5/2 \u003d -√(5/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n5x^2 + 25x + 25 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(13)/2 - 7/2, -√(13)/2 - 7/2", "explanation": "Move c to the other side\n3x^2 + 21x \u003d -27\nDivide through by a\nx^2 + 7x \u003d -9\nComplete the Square\nx^2 + 7x + 49/4 \u003d 13/4\nFactor\n(x + 7/2)^2 \u003d 13/4\nExtract the square root\nx + 7/2 \u003d √(13/4) or x + 7/2 \u003d -√(13/4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x by completing the square:\n3x^2 + 21x + 27 \u003d 0", "type": "text"}
]}